如果你想过上美好的生活
If you want a life better than what you got,
我会尽可能地帮助你
I will help you get to the other side.
-我做不到  -喂
- I can't. - Hello?
这是你第一次开枪吗
Is this your first time firing your weapon?
是啊
Yeah.
你想找人聊天的话我随时奉陪
I'm around any time you need to talk.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
终于
Finally.
3.25美元
$3.25.
我有无数次都想来找你聊聊
I wanted to come talk to you, like, a million times.
是吗
Uh-huh.
我戒了
I'm clean.
戒了一个月了
30 days.
那恭喜了  娜迪亚
Congratulations, Nadia.
真心恭喜
Sincerely.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你帮我
For trying with me.
我知道这种事不是一蹴而就的
Look, I know it took a few times,
但是你为我做的事我都记在心里
but what you did for me, it really stuck.
照顾好自己
Take care of yourself.
橄榄球联盟他们有种御寒马甲
In the NFL, they've got these cold weather vests...
-是吗  -是用电池的还是什么
- Yeah? - Battery-operated or something,
让在场外区的人也能好好保暖
to keep 'em nice and toasty on the sidelines.
这样啊
Yeah.
衣服轻而薄  刚好适合我们穿
Lightweight, thin material, perfect for us.
这种事警署里应该找谁说
Who do I talk to in the district about something like that?
我可以帮你查查...
Well, let me look that up for you, I'll--
等我上网
Once I get to a computer.
这绝对是个好主意
You know it's a good idea.
-啊  -不好意思
- Oh! - Sorry.
-你好  -你好
- What's up, bro? - How you doin', man?
你拉链没拉
Your fly's open.
希腊神话中的美少年
因自恋水中倒影  相思而死
那耳喀索斯  你过来
Hey, Narcissus, come on over here.
-你说谁  -过来
- Who? - Come over here.
什么事
Yeah?
周五晚你有空吗
What do you got going on Friday night?
我需要你帮个忙
I need you.
私人问题
Off the books.
-我该担心吗  -不用
- Should I be worried? - No.
怎么  你有什么秘密吗
Why? You got something to hide?
不是  我就是想弄明白你想让我干什么
No, I'm jut trying to figure out what you're asking me.
不是想让你干什么  我是在通知你
I'm not asking you; I'm telling you,
周五晚你就知道了
and you'll find out Friday.
你穿好看点  到时候找我就行了
So meet out here and wear something nice.
-穿好看点  -对
- Something nice? - Yeah.
你也听到了吗
Are you hearing this?
马上行动
We gotta move.
-怎么了  -有大屠杀
- Hey, what's going on? - Massacre.
-给你  -警探
- There you go. - Detective.
现在是什么情况
All right, where are we at so far?
四名保安死亡  一名受伤
The four guards are dead, and one guy's wounded.
凶手抢走了什么
What'd they get?
八百万现金
Eight million in cash.
从日本长野县来的国际货币运输船
International currency shipment from Nagano, Japan,
开往拉萨尔的联邦储备局
headed down to the federal reserve on Lasalle.
他们顺利通关了
They cleared customs fine,
然后现金就被运来这里
and then the money came here
等待装上运钞车
to be loaded onto an armored car.
可以问讯受伤人员吗
Can the survivor tell us anything?
可以  唯一状况稳定的人是卢卡斯•佩尔科
Yeah. The one guy that's stable is Lukas Perko.
他是仓库经理
He's the warehouse manager
还有保安队长艾瑞克·冈萨雷斯
and Eric Gonzalez, head of security.
好  你去问他
All right, you grab him.
-我们去问佩尔科  -好
- We'll talk to Perko. - Okay.
你还好吗
How you doing?
不知道
I don't know.
他们说子弹把我打穿了
They say it's a through and through.
能让我们单独待一会儿吗
Hey, can you give us a minute?
好的
Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
你都看到什么了
What'd you see?
他们有四个人
Four of 'em.
黑色连帽衫  戴着面具
Black hoodie, masks,
一身黑衣  蒙着头巾
dark shades, bandanas.
他们疯狂扫射
They lit the place up, man.
一切都那么突然
It all happened just like... that.
他们进来时你在哪里
And where were you when they came in?
我当时在厕所
I was in the john,
跑出来的时候
and I come runnin' out.
就看到一个人拿着枪朝我过来
And I saw a gun swing my way.
当时就跟放鞭炮一样
I heard sounds like firecrackers.
我中弹然后倒下了
I got hit. I dropped.
他们肯定以为你被打死了
I guess they thought you were dead.
应该是吧
Yeah, I guess.
罪犯的身高体重呢
Height? Weight?
你还看到什么了
Anything else?
我看到他们的额头和脖子了
I caught a glimpse of their foreheads and necks.
可以肯定都是黑人
Black guys, for sure.
怎么会这样呢
It doesn't make any sense.
明天是雷金纳德的生日
It was Reginald's birthday tomorrow.
我们本来打算一起去粉色猴子酒店庆祝的
We were gonna go to the Pink Monkey, all of us.
你都看到什么了
What'd you see?
当时我在后面的办公室里
I was in my office in the back of the building.
听到了突突声
I heard, like, a pop, pop, pop.
我到这里时  就...
And by the time I got here, it was--
大家都...  我想...
Everyone was just-- I mean, I tried to
用手抱住廷克的头
hold Tinker's head with my hand,
但血还是止不住地流
but I couldn't keep the blood in.
我们需要看看你们的监控录像
We're gonna need to see all of your security footage.
好的  没问题
Yeah, whatever you need.
保安那边有什么收获
What did you get from the security guy?
他好像被吓得不轻
He seemed in genuine shock.
你们那边呢
What about your guy?
他们中肯定有一个人在撒谎
Eight million reasons I can think of why one of 'em is lying.
你和鲁塞克怎么回事
What's up with you and Ruzek?
什么意思
What do you mean?
之前你不小心撞到他时
I mean, you looked like you were at the seventh grade dance
你就像舞会上的小女生一样惊慌
when you bumped into him earlier.
现在我提到他
Now, I'm sayin' his name,
你又脸色不对劲
and you don't look much better.
我们...
It's, uh...
我也不知道怎么回事
I don't know what it is.
我可以直说吗
Permission to speak freely?
好哇  我听着不爽的话
Sure, as long as I have permission
你同意让我踹你屁股就行
to kick you in the ass if I don't like what you say.
可以啊
Okay.
如果你打算靠睡男人进情报组
If your big plan is to sleep your way into intelligence,
我觉得睡他好像没用
I'm not sure if that's the right guy to make that happen.
我开玩笑的
I'm jokin'. I'm jokin'.
-滚一边儿去  阿特沃特  -我逗你玩呢
- Get off me, Atwater. - I'm playin'.
我说笑呢  说笑呢
I didn't mean it. I didn't mean it.
佩尔科在那里干了两年
All right, Perko's been with the company for two years.
没有犯罪记录
He's got no criminal record.
但他进过少管所
He did have a juvey one, though.
佩尔科15岁时和他的兄弟多米尼克
Perko and his brother Dominik got pinched at 15
因一桩贩卖冰毒的案件被抓
on a drug conspiracy for selling meth.
他在18岁时被强制性释放
He had a mandatory release at 18
之后一直规规矩矩的
and stayed on the straight and narrow,
但他兄弟之后还为一个克罗地亚黑帮贩毒
but the brother kept dealing for a Croatian gang,
叫做二三会
the Two-Threes.
他兄弟被判入狱八年  目前正在服刑
Brother's currently serving eight years at Stateville.
好
Okay.
他们有六个摄像头
So they had six video cameras,
你们肯定觉得大有作用  对吗
which you'd think would be aces, right?
但是你们看  一号和二号摄像头
But, as you can see, cameras one and two,
嫌疑人离镜头太远
the crew stays too far out of frame
无法提供有效的身份信息
to be of any useful identification.
三号和四号  他们都不在镜头内
Three and four, they stay out of frame all together.
五号  他们背对着镜头
And on five, they keep their backs to the camera.
六号  他们无法避开的那个
And six, the one camera that they can't avoid,
很巧地被门给挡住了
well, it's conveniently obscured by the gate.
这肯定是内部作案
There's no way this isn't an inside job.
我跟南区的警察聊了聊
I talked to the dicks over at area south.
有个寻访警探曾经询问过一名卡车司机
One of the canvassing detectives interviewed a trucker
他说他看到一辆厢式货车从案发地点逃走
who said that he saw a panel van fleeing the scene.
-牌照呢  -没有
- Tags? - Nothing.
不过他看到两名男子摘下了面罩
Except he saw two of the guys remove their masks.
他没有看清他们的样子
Now, he didn't get a good look at their faces,
但他说他们都是白人男性
but he said they were both Caucasian males.
所以佩尔科说谎了
So Perko lied.
还用"黑人干的"这么老掉牙的借口
The old "black guys did it" defense.
他在芝加哥医院的急诊室
He's in the E.R. at Chicago Med.
我想先去查这条线索  老大
Yeah, I'd like first crack at this one, boss.
你这是想证明自己吗  萨姆纳
You lookin' to prove yourself, Sumner?
我已经准备好让他开口了
I'm ready to grill him till he rolls.
很好
Good.
跟安东尼奥一起去
Take Antonio with you.
-艾莉  -你好  杰
- Allie. - Hi, Jay.
你好
Hey.
我刚才来这附近帮我爸爸取本书
I was just picking up a book for my dad up the street,
然后我就想我可以...
and I thought I would just--
跟你在一起很开心
I had a great time.
我也很高兴你顺路过来看我
And I'm glad you stopped by, okay?
-那明晚见  -明晚见
- Tomorrow night then? - Tomorrow night.
说吧
And?
只是个熟人
She's just a girl I know.
你跟那个消防员怎么样了
How's it going with the fireman?
我们打算慢慢来
We're taking things slow.
你们是警探吧
The detectives, right?
我刚刚还在想...
I was just thinking--
我们已经知道是内部作案了
We know it was an inside job,
所以我们怀疑
so we started wondering,
会不会就是那个在别人被打成筛子的时候
could it be the one guy who walks away
恰好走开的家伙干的呢
while everyone else catches a dozen bullets?
内部作案
Inside job?
也许是个以前进过少管所
Maybe it's the guy with a juvey record
现在兄弟在监狱的家伙
and a brother in Stateville.
我当时只是卖了几颗小药丸
Hey, I was just a shorty.
又或者是撒谎说罪犯是黑人的那个家伙
Or maybe it's the guy who lied about the crew being black.
好吧  听着
Okay, look.
开枪打我的那个人  我认识他
The guy who shot me, I recognized him.
他的头巾滑了下来
His--his bandana slipped.
他是我邻居  但我不知道他的名字
He's from my neighborhood, but I don't know his name.
他是二三会的成员
I mean, he's in the Two-Three's.
他们势力很广
These guys, they got a lot of reach.
我要是多嘴  他们会在监狱找我兄弟麻烦
I roll, they find my brother in the prison.
想象一下  你这张脸出现在
Imagine your face for the world to see
字典里"种族主义者"词条的旁边
next to the word "racist" in the dictionary.
好吧
Okay.
丹尼斯·诺瓦克
Dennis Novak.
N-O-V-A-K  这么拼吗
N-O-V-A-K?
对
Yeah.
东皮尔森的丹尼斯·诺瓦克吗
Dennis Novak from East Pilsen?
他的团伙卖大麻  摇头丸
Look, his crew sells kush, X,
就是现在市面上的各种垃圾玩意儿
whatever they're calling junk these days.
但他是个不入流的毒贩子
He's a low-level jab slinger.
他做不了这么大的案子
It's way out of his league.
他说的是实话
He's telling the truth.
好吧
Okay.
去找你们的线人  毒虫  赌鬼
Reach out to your CI's, the hypes, the lot lizards.
看看这家伙能在我的城市里躲到哪儿去
Find out where in my city this guy thinks he can hide.
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
我的错
Yeah, my bad.
警长  我很愿意帮你
Sarge, I'm willing to help you and everything,
但你得告诉我到底是什么事
but you gotta tell me what's going on here.
我不得不完成老爸协议了
I gotta close the dad deal.
你说什么
The--the what now?
我习惯住在林肯公园的一栋好房子里
I'm accustomed to living in a nice house in Lincoln Park,
但我当警察拿的工资负担不起
a house I can't afford on my CPD salary.
然后呢
Okay.
我爸很有钱
My dad is very wealthy.
和投资银行家差不多
Investment banker wealthy.
甚至能上《福布斯》封面
Cover of Forbes wealthy.
真的吗
Really?
我是他一直未婚的老闺女
I'm his older single daughter who's never been married.
每年我们都要玩一套老把戏
We do this dance every year
我会把我的新未婚夫带去吃晚餐
where I bring my new fiance to dinner
告诉他这个就是我的真命天子
and tell him I'm sure this is the one.
然后他就给我一张支票说他为我骄傲
He then writes me a check and tells me he's proud of me.
我们都在这件事上装样子走过场
We're both just going through the motions at this point,
但他这人很保守
but he's old-fashioned,
如果我不再玩这套把戏
and I don't want to think about what would happen
不知道会怎样
if I don't play the game.
好了  无需多说
All right, say no more.
我懂了  明白
I get it. I do.
只是  你觉得他会相信吗
It's just I--you think he's going to buy this?
他为什么不信
Why wouldn't he?
那个...
Well, the, uh...
年龄差距
The age difference.
你觉得我有多老
Exactly how old do you think I am?
不知道
I have no idea.
星期五
Friday.
穿得好看点
Dress nicely.
好吧
Okay.
你要一个人待会儿吗
You need a moment?
那好  来吧
All right, come on.
佩尔科要出院了
Perko's about to walk from the hospital.
汉克想让我们盯着他
Hank wants us to keep an eye on him.
去哪儿都比在这儿好
Anywhere's better than here.
诺瓦克就在这儿躲着
This is where Novak holes up.
二三会代替银行把这个地方收了
Instead of the bank taking over, the Two-Threes did.
所以根本不需要搜查令
Which makes no warrant necessary.
芝加哥警署
Chicago P.D.!
发现尸体
Bodies!
掩护
Cover!
我盯着左边的房间  快去
I got the door on the left. Go!
又发现三具尸体
I've got three more!
-安全  -安全
- Clear! - Clear!
安全
Clear!
发现了几个这种东西
Well, found a couple of these.
就算这里原来藏着钱  现在也没了
If there was money here, it's gone now..
也许某人想多分点钱
Maybe somebody wanted a bigger piece of the pie for himself.
三个人身上都有二三会的标记
Three of these men have Two-Threes' ink.
看看这个
Look at this guy.
-他不是克罗地亚人  -圣犹大·塔德奥
- He ain't Croatian. - San Judas Tadeo.
他在哥伦比亚是个贩毒大咖
He's a big narcosaint in Colombia.
没错
That's right.
我们找到了两种不同类型的子弹
So we've got two different types of rounds.
发现了手枪打出子弹的九个角位
We've got the nine mils from the pistols,
然后从墙上挖出了几个子弹
and then I dug a couple slugs out of the wall.
我觉得这是0.22中空弹
I think that' a 0.22 hollow point.
杀手用的子弹
It's an assassin's bullet.
十有八九他进来时碰上了哥伦比亚的杀手
10 to 1 he came in with a Colombian hit squad,
胸部中了两枪
caught two in the chest,
倒下后  他的朋友就不管他了
and his amigos left him where he fell.
查查这位波哥大[哥伦比亚首都]先生的指纹
So run Mr. Bogota's prints.
看看能有什么发现
See if we find anything at all.
我们得知道到底是谁
We need a name.
他买了咖啡
He picks up his coffee,
去了药房
goes to the pharmacy,
取了干洗衣服
picks up the dry cleaning.
盯佩尔科的梢完全是浪费时间  埃尔
Tailing Perko was a complete wank, Al.
总有露出马脚的时候
That is till it isn't.
毫无意义
That is meaningless.
所以你跟温迪到底要怎么样
So what'd you decide about Wendy?
我只是想慢慢来  你知道吗
Oh, I'm just takin' it one day at a time, you know?
不  我不知道
No, I don't know.
真不知道
Not really.
我得问问你
Hey, I got to ask you.
普拉特警长  她出柜了吗
Sergeant Platt, is she out of the closet?
我觉得对那个女人
I make it my mission to know as little
了解的越少越好
about that woman as possible.
她让我假扮她男友去见她父亲
She's making me be her beard to meet her father.
不想让爸爸知道自己是同性恋什么的  这我理解
I get it, you don't want your dad to know you're gay.
也无所谓  可我不理解她为什么这样
That's fine. I just don't get it with her.
我高中有个朋友  叫特拉维斯·怀特
High school friend of mine, Travis White.
是个足球运动员
Hell of a football player.
获得了圣母大学的全额奖学金  长得很帅
Full ride at Notre Dame, the works.
但生来就是同性恋  所有人都知道
But gay as the day is long, and everybody knew it.
他宁愿和他男朋友搬去朝鲜
Now, rather than come out to his parents,
也不愿在父母面前出柜
he moves to Korea with his boyfriend.
现在  他每年回来一趟
Now, he comes back once a year
但告诉他的父母
but tells his parents
他在朝鲜的女朋友害怕坐飞机
that his girlfriend out there is afraid of flying.
朝鲜
Korea.
他父母人很好
Now--and his parents are nice.
看看这个人
Look at this guy.
赚区区一美元真不容易啊
Man, anything for a buck, huh?
离我的车远点  好吗
Hey! Get away from the car, would you?
搞什么
What the fuck?
天呐
Whoa.
搞什么
What the hell?
站住
Hey!
我去追那个擦车窗的人
I got the squeegee guy.
站住
Stop!
趴下  趴下
Get down, get down!
坚持住  伙计
Hang in there, buddy.
站住
Stop!
芝加哥警署  快闪开
Chicago P.D.! Out of the way!
快  快  快走
Go, go, go!
妈的
Son of a bitch.
有辆车接应那个混蛋
Bastard had a car waiting.
这个人怎么样了
How's this guy?
不太好
Not good.
天啊
Jeez.
是汽油
It's gasoline.
当敌人进入某处时故意烧毁
破坏及移除任何可能对敌人有用的东西
哥伦比亚人这次要用使用焦土战略了
The Colombians are going scorched earth on this.
千真万确
Literally.
我觉得他们是想把这个人和他的所有东西
I think they were hoping to torch this guy in his car
都在车里烧光
along with everything with him.
但我在他手机被烧毁之前
But I managed to put out the flames
扑灭了火苗
before his cell phone was destroyed.
给我吧
I'll take that.
我以为你相信佩尔科
I thought you said you believed Perko.
在克罗地亚的帮派问题上  我是相信他
About the Croatian gang, yeah.
但哥伦比亚人的事  我不清楚
But this Colombian thing, I don't know how it adds up.
我有个想法
I got a theory.
佩尔科知道将会有八百万收入囊中
Perko knows about the $8 million coming in,
决定是时候建他的退休基金了
decides it's time to set up his retirement fund.
嫌疑人  卢卡斯·佩尔科
于是雇他的克罗地亚老朋友来取钱
Hires his old Croatian friends to come and take it.
唯一的问题是
Only problem is,
哥伦比亚人发现了  决定来个螳螂捕蝉
the Colombians found out and decided to rob the robbers.
好吧  但哥伦比亚人是怎么知道的
Okay, but how did the Colombians find out?
有个号码连续十一次
Perko's cell had the same number call it
给佩尔科打电话
the last 11 times.
打给州法院  安排个法官
Call the state, line up a judge.
你去准备申请调查手机记录的搜查证
You start writing up a warrant for that phone.
不用
Don't need to.
电话全是从斯泰特维尔监狱打来的
The calls all came from inside Stateville Prison.
除非你们是我的新律师
Unless you guys are my new attorneys,
否则我没什么好说的
I got nothing to say.
你哥哥死了
Your brother is dead.
像块牛排一样在18大街
He was lit up like a barbecue grill
路中间被烤熟了
in the middle of 18th Street.
我不信
I don't believe you.
是哥伦比亚人干的
Colombians did it.
八百万没了  小子  没了
The $8 million is gone, baby, gone.
抢劫是你的主意  对吗
Robbery was your idea, yeah?
你哥哥跟你说了他在哪里
Your brother told you about where he worked,
干什么工作  因为你们关系很好
what he did, 'cause you two were close.
你给他和二三帮的人牵线认识
You connected him with the Two-Threes,
你被关进来之前就是把毒品卖给他们的
who you sold drugs for prior to getting locked up.
哥伦比亚人吗
Colombians?
没错
Yeah.
他们会把牵扯其中的人都赶尽杀绝
They're killing anyone and everyone involved in this plan.
所以你得告诉我们你是怎么
So you need to tell us what deal you made
出卖的你哥哥
to double-cross your brother,
否则我们会把那十宗谋杀都安在你头上
or we're gonna charge you federally for all ten murders,
然后我就能听到自己最喜欢的两个词了
and then I get to hear my two favorite words...
等等  听好了...
wait, listen, wait, here it comes:
"死刑"
"death penalty."
你得给我换个囚室
You gotta get me a new cell.
让我从那间搬出来
Move me out of that block.
你想讨价还价
Whoa, you want to negotiate,
那就得先证明自己有用啊
then you got to give us something.
不  你不懂
No, you don't understand.
我的狱友是哥伦比亚人
My cellmate is Colombian.
是拉丁君主帮的杀手
He's a big time killer with the Latin Kings.
他一定是听到我说的话了
He must've heard me talking.
他叫米盖尔·奥特加
His name is Miguel Ortega.
我没有出卖卢卡斯
I didn't double-cross Lukas.
我爱他
I loved him.
你们得帮我
You gotta help me.
那犯人叫米盖尔·奥特加
The prisoner's name is Miguel Ortega.
-囚号452-8512  -好的
- Convict number 452-8512. - Okay.
我要接到过他电话的所有人的名字和住址
I need the name and address of every person he's called,
探监人员  或者过去72小时内寄信的人
visited, or sent mail to the last 72 hours.
马上查
I'm on it.
我们要给多米尼克·佩尔科换间囚室吗
We gonna move Dominik Perko to a new cell?
他自作的孽
He made his bed.
自己受吧
Let him bleed in it.
查到了
Score one for the home team.
米盖尔·奥特加被探视过九次
Miguel Ortega's been visited nine times
打了四通电话给自己在
and made four phone calls to his main man
拉丁君主帮的亲信  罗洛·拉米雷斯
in the Latin Kings, Rolo Ramirez.
这些都是现在跟着他的副手
And these are his active lieutenants.
那是那个流浪汉
That's the homeless guy.
-放火的那个  -这个吗
- The torcher. - This guy?
你确定吗
You sure?
确定  头儿
I'm certain, boss.
如果你是拉丁君主帮的
You're the Latin Kings.
抢了抢劫犯  拿走了八百万
You rob the robbers, get away with 8 mill.
为什么要杀了佩尔科
Why waste Perko?
除非他知道了不该知道的
Well, you wouldn't do it unless he knew something
否则不会这样
he wasn't supposed to.
但他是跟克罗地亚人混的
But he was tied to the Croatians,
不是哥伦比亚人
not the Colombians.
叫"冈萨雷斯"这名的会是哪国人
What's the nationality of the name Gonzalez?
绝对不是克罗地亚人
It's not Croatian.
你好  我们预约了
Hi, we have an appointment.
不如你出去转转吧
Why don't you step outside for a second?
别怕  没事
Come on, it's okay.
我准备打电话给...
Hey, I was gonna call--
你在这工作多久了  三周吗
You been working here, what, three weeks?
差不多
Something like that.
罗洛·拉米雷斯在哪里
Where's Rolo Ramirez?
你也看到刚才我们动摄像头了吧
You notice what we did with the camera, right?
监控坏了以后
And bad things happen
总是会有不好的事发生
when security cameras are rendered ineffective,
你说呢
wouldn't you say?
我...
I--
兄弟
Bro...
我们知道你是在拉丁君主帮
we know Ramirez put you in this job
听到抢劫的风声之后  被拉米雷斯安排来的
after the Latin Kings caught wind of the robbery plans.
坐吧
Have a seat.
你想拉自己一把的话  就趁现在
You want to help yourself, now's the time.
否则  那摄像头还是会对着墙...
Otherwise, we leave that camera facing the wall...
之后发生什么  听天由命
and whatever happens, happens.
好吧  我不知道他在哪
Okay, I don't know where he is,
但知道怎么找到他
but I know how to get to him.
罗洛  他喜欢高档的应召女
Rolo, he likes to use high-end whores.
白妞
White chicks.
用电话叫妓女
He uses a call service.
哪一家
Which one?
禅宗欲女
Zen Dolls.
罗洛刚叫了两个妓女
Rolo just ordered two hookers.
有人接她们去特定地点
They get picked up and dropped off at a location,
所以我们要派一个警察去装妓女
so we're going to put a cop in with one of their whores.
也就是说...
That means--
我去
I'll do it.
好
Okay.
去换衣服
Go get dressed.
剩下的人装备好  准备动手  去吧
The rest of us suit up and get ready for the meet. Let's go.
她抢了你饭碗哦
She beat you to the punch, huh?
她想逞英雄就随她去
If she wants to step up, let her step up.
你就是不想让我们看见你穿裙子
You just didn't want anybody seeing you in a skirt.
我不确定会不会闪瞎大家
I'm not sure anyone would enjoy that.
不会的  你乱说的吧
Oh, no, well, that's not really true.
我是说
You know, I mean,
因为你总是谦虚
'cause you're just always so self-deprecating.
我还有事要忙
I've got stuff to do.
她还嫩
She's green.
我觉得我们不该让她随便跟哪个妓女一起
I don't think we should just put her in with random skank.
你说禅宗欲女  是吗
You said Zen Dolls, right?
对
That's right.
我认识里面的一个人
I know somebody who works there.
曾经在那里工作
Or did.
好  去安排吧
All right, set it up.
其实你没必要这么做
You know you don't have to do this.
我想向博伊特证明自己
I want to prove myself to Voight.
我得干件大的
I got to take big swings.
你比任何人都应该明白这点
Now, you of all people know that to be true.
你...
Just...
保护好我
cover my ass.
会保护好的
Covered.
什么时候来接
What time's the pick up?
15分钟后
15 minutes.
好的
All right.
你确定要这么做吗
You sure you're up for this?
确定
Yeah.
好
All right.
你只需要带我们的警官进去
You just need to get our officer inside.
她一找到罗洛·拉米雷斯
And as soon as she I.D.s Rolo Ramirez,
就会发信号让我们进去
she'll signal us in.
躲在角落里不要引起别人注意  明白吗
Get in a corner and make yourself small, all right?
好的
Okay.
非常抱歉我以前让你失望了
I'm really sorry I let you down before.
重新做人  就从现在开始
Fresh start, right here, right now.
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Yeah.
来吧
Come on.
-伙计们  这是娜迪亚  -你们好
- Guy's this is Nadia. - Hi.
这是金
That's Kim.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
小时候你爸爸碰过你吗
Your daddy ever touch you when you were a kid?
什么
What?
熄掉你眼里的光彩
Turn the light off in your eyes.
对了
Yeah.
我们准备好了
We're ready.
等一下
Wait a second.
窃听器有故障  我需要一个小时
The wire's glitching. I'm gonna need an hour.
我们没有一个小时  吉恩
We don't have an hour, Jin.
没关系
No, it's fine.
我们不需要这东西
We don't need it.
我看到拉米雷斯就给你们打电话
I get eyes on Ramirez, I'll call you.
好了  我们行动吧
All right, let's do it.
女士下命令了
You heard the lady.
瞧啊
Look at that.
真是绅士啊
A real gentleman.
坐下
Sit down.
Sit down!
这怎么回事
What the hell is this?
罗洛叫了姑娘来
Rolo ordered some girls.
罗洛不在这里
Rolo ain't here.
马上过来
Not yet.
站起来
Get up!
没和你说话
I'm not talking to you!
坐下
Sit down!
来一口
Do a rail.
怎么了  宝贝
What's that, baby?
来一口可卡因
Do a rail of coke.
不  我和莱西已经不吸那玩意儿了
Nah, see, me and Lacy, we don't that anymore.
-我们戒了  -对
- We're clean. - Yeah.
伙计  她们不想要可卡因
Man, they don't want the coke,
就随她们去吧
they don't want it.
干嘛非要浪费在这些婊子身上
Why waste it on these bitches?
她们不吸  说不定她们是缉毒警
If they don't want it, what if they're narcs!
好  老大  这是派对
Hey, hey, papi, it's a party.
我们就该放开来玩  对吧
We're just gonna party, okay?
我明白的
I got it.
没问题
It's cool.
我愿意来  好吗
I'll do it, all right?
爽  爽  太爽了
Damn. Damn. Damn.
罗洛来之前我要不要跟你先来一发
Maybe I'll let you ride this d before Rolo gets here, huh?
你想怎么样都行  宝贝
Whatever you want, baby.
你想怎么样都行
Whatever you want.
我们走
Let's go.
什么好货
What's good?
你们不带我就先开始了吗
You startin' the party without me or what?
你好啊  罗洛
'Sup, Rolo?
你介意我先试玩一下这妞吗
You mind if I take this one for a test drive?
好  去吧
Yeah, go ahead.
-我们走  -我要拿上包
- Let's go. - Uh, I need my purse.
宝贝  你有避孕套吗
Oh, yeah, baby, you got a condom?
我猜没有
I don't think so.
所以我需要我的包
Then I need my purse.
-给你  宝贝  -谢谢  亲爱的
- Here you go, baby. - Thanks, darlin'.
你要去哪  坐下
Hey, where you goin'? Sit down.
派对在这里  宝贝
The party's right here, baby.
罗洛在这里
Rolo's here.
还有五个在前面  一个在后面
Five others in the front, one in the back.
快点
Hurry.
给我五分钟
Give me five.
警察
Police!
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
快点  快点
Do it now! Do it now!
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
趴到地上  趴到地上
On the ground! On the ground!
趴到地上
On the ground!
-趴到地上  -趴下
- On the ground! - Get down!
放下枪
Drop the gun!
是你
You!
救救我
Help me.
放下枪  伙计
Drop the gun, man!
放下
Put it down!
不许动  不许动
Freeze! Freeze!
好的  好的
All right. All right. All right.
趴下
Get your ass down!
伯吉斯
Burgess!
-你还好吗  -我没事
- Are you all right? - I'm okay.
你受伤了吗
Are you injured?
去吧  快去追
Go! Just go!
嫌犯逃跑
Target on the move!
房子前面
Front of the house!
是放火的那个凶手
Torcher, the assassin.
他向南逃跑了
He's fleeing south on foot!
你去开车
You get the car!
我先跑去追他
I've got him on foot!
没事了
Hey, it's okay.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
-我没办法  -我知道
- I had to. - I know.
但我之前都戒了的
But I was clean.
对不起
Sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
站住
Stop!
离开这[西语]
Fuera de aqui!
还好吗
You okay?
所有巡警注意  嫌犯徒步逃出
All patrols, suspect's out on foot
南奥尔巴尼2600号
fleeing 2600 South Albany.
南奥尔巴2119组汇报
Unit 2119 on South Albany.
没有嫌犯踪影
No sign of suspect.
看来有人逃脱了
Looks like one of us got away.
闭嘴
Shut up.
伯吉斯  你还好吗
Burgess, you all right?
还好  长官
Yes, sir.
起来
Get up.
站起来
Get up!
给他松开
Disposal.
把她带出去
Get her out of here.
所有人都出去
Everybody out of the house!
看着我
Look at me.
那八百万在哪
Where's the $8 million?
在你屁眼里
It's up your ass.
-是吗  -是啊
- It is? - Yeah.
右手还是左手
You right-handed or left-handed?
问你老母去
Ask your mother, huh?
听着  我不认识你  老兄
Look, uh, I don't know you, bro,
但你应该知道我
but you should know me.
我是汉克·博伊特
I'm Hank Voight.
我从不吓唬人
I don't make idle threats.
你不告诉我那八百万在哪
You're going to tell me where the $8 million is,
我就把你的手塞池子里搅烂
or we're going to put your hand down that sink.
然后你的脚  我会把你整张脸都塞进去
Then your feet. I'll put your whole damn face.
听清楚了吗  我看起来像吓唬你吗
Do you hear me? I look like I'm bluffin'?
告诉我那八百万在哪
Tell me where the eight is.
那八百万在哪
Tell me where the eight is!
我说
Okay!
我说  我说  我说
Okay! Okay! Okay!
这比我一年赚的都多
I think that's more than I make a year.
谁通知的内务部
Who called Internal Affairs?
我会自己查清楚
I'd be curious to know that myself.
让我们单独谈谈
Give us a minute.
要数数吗
Want to count it?
你知道银行每分钱都投保了
You know the banks are insured for every penny.
然后呢
And?
我们第一次见时  你说我们是合作关系
When we first met, you said this was gonna be a partnership.
合作也有很多种
There's a lot of different kinds of partnerships.
7.9万就是其中一种
7.9 million different kinds.
也许是7.8万
Or 7.8.
只要是你想的  肯定都可以
Any kind you want there to be, I'll bet you could find it.
证明给我看
Voucher it.
每一分钱
Every penny.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
干得很不错  伯吉斯
You did well, Burgess.
谢谢你  警探
Thank you, Detective.
别在琳德赛面前这么做
Don't let Lindsay see you do that.
好
Okay.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
跟一只斗牛犬干了三个回合
I went three rounds with a pit bull.
好吧
Right.
好吧  这下有意思了
Well, this'll be interesting.
我来开车
I'll drive.
我当时坐在机场里
And I'm sitting in the airport,
他问我"你了解管道装置吗"
and he says to me, "Do you know anything about pipe fixtures?"
我说"知道一点"
I say, "A little."
然后他斜眼看我
So now he looks at me sideways.
我又说"我想我应该知道"
"I guess I should," I say.
"西尔斯大厦所有管道都是我装的"
"I put all the pipes into the Sears Tower."
是的  "是的  我懂一点管道"
Yeah, "Yeah, I know a little bit about pipes."
所以他说"我想也是"
So he says, "Yeah, I guess you do."
然后他邀请我为他做事
And he offers me to come work for him.
很慷慨的邀请我  你懂的
And that's very generous, you know.
但我说
But I say,
"卡森先生  我现在过得很好
"Mr. Carson, I'm doing just fine.
也许你该来为我工作”
Maybe you should come to work for me."
你喜欢这牛排吗  亚当
How do you like that steak, Adam?
超好吃  先生
Damn good, sir.
罗伯特
Robert.
请叫我罗伯特
Robert, please.
罗伯特
Robert.
你和特鲁迪是在工作上认识的
So you and Trudy met at work?
是的  没错
We did, yeah.
你是因为工作擦伤的吗
That how you got those bruises?
只是服务和保护人民  罗伯特
Just serving and protecting, Robert.
我问你件事  亚当
Let me ask you something, Adam.
尽管问
Go right ahead.
我最喜欢我女儿特鲁迪哪一点
What do you like most about my daughter Trudy?
老爸
Dad.
我最喜欢的是
Well, I would have to say that I like the fact
她非常了解自己
that she knows exactly who she is.
她从不让别人占到自己的便宜
That she doesn't take crap from anybody,
我指所有人
and I mean anybody.
她是个...
She's a...
她是...
She's just a...
她是个铁娘子  我的小娘子
She's a tough cookie, my little cookie.
可能这点像你  先生
Probably like you, sir.
好吧  很好
Well, that's fine.
这...
That is...
很好
just fine.
敬特鲁迪
To Trudy.
谢谢
Thank you.
敬你  宝贝
To you, baby.
好酒
Ah, that's good.
谢谢
Thank you.
你再吃一盘  这是命令
You're having seconds. That's an order.
盖尔  我饱了
Gail, I'm full.
我看你可是越来越瘦
You look like you're wasting away.
你不能跟这个女人的说不的  杰
You can't tell this woman no, Jay.
都这么久了  你也该知道了吧
You should've learned that by now.
我要想减肥只有搬出去住
The only way I could lose weight was to move away.
别以为我没看到你都没怎么吃
Yeah, don't think I didn't notice you hardly ate.
我都吃了一大盘了好吗
I had a full plate.
还有人要喝红酒吗
Does anyone want more wine?
好的
Please.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Yes, thank you. - Thank you.
他现在好多了
You should see that one.
他今天去棚屋那边建新的小木屋了
He was out in the shed today, building new cabinets.
我都不知道有多久没见他去那边了
I haven't seen him out there in I don't know how long.
太好了
That's great.
盖尔  你把软木塞放哪里了
Gail, where'd you put the cork screw?
我来了
Coming.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming.
他们看到你都很高兴
They light up when they see you.
客气了
It's my pleasure.
你什么时候回去
So when do you go back?
明天
Tomorrow.
知道我找到什么了吗
Do you know what I found?
毕业舞会上你俩的合影
A picture of you two from prom.
天啊
Oh, God.
我一直以为你俩有戏呢
Ah, I always thought the two of you should've made a go of it.
妈
Mom!
怎么了
What?
快给我倒酒吧
Just pour the wine.
你搬回来住吧  艾莉
Why don't you move back, Allie?
待在菲尼克斯有什么好的
Phoenix has nothing for you.
你的家人都在这里
Your family is here.
是啊  艾莉  搬回来住吧
Yeah, Allie, why don't you move back?
可能吧
Maybe I will.
你车停在哪里了
Where are you parked?
那边那辆福特皮卡
It's this Ford pick-up right over here.
谢谢你了
Well, thanks for that.
不用谢  今晚很开心
No, I had a good time.
谢谢你邀请我
You know, thank you for inviting me.
你爸爸  看上去人不错
Your dad, he seems-- you know, he seems great.
他是个吹牛大王
He's a blowhard.
但是了解他的话就会发现其实人不错
But he's not too bad once you get to know him.
那你搞定了吗
Hey, you seal the deal?
他给了我一个信封
He gave me an envelope.
我还没打开看呢
I haven't looked at it yet.
我想问你件事  警长
I gotta ask you something, Sarge.
你为什么还不告诉他你是同性恋
Why haven't you told him you're gay?
同性恋
Gay?
是啊  我觉得...
Yeah, I just-- I think--
我知道还轮不到我来说
And I know I'm speaking out of school here,
但是我觉得他不会介意的
but I think he'd be cool with it.
他看上去...
He seem like a--
我不是同性恋
I'm not gay.
什么
What?
我念警校的时候跟班上一半男生都上过床
I did half the guys in my class in the academy.
我只是没找到合适的人
Just because I haven't found someone worth a damn
结婚稳定下来
to settle down with,
并不意味着...
that doesn't mean--
好吧
Oh, okay.
真是...
This is--
是啊
Yeah.
确实如此
You're damn right it is.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
就当我刚才什么都没说
Just forget I said anything, Sarge.
当我什么都没说
Forget I said that.
好  我也不会跟你未婚妻说
Yeah, I'll forget to say anything to your fiancee
你跟伯吉斯上过床
about you shacking up with Burgess.
-我们没...  -但是你有这个想法
- We didn't-- - Yeah, but you want to.
等等   等等
Wait. Wait. Wait.
好吧
Okay.
我们明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见就明天见
No, I'll see you tomorrow.
好吧
Yeah.
准备好了吗
You ready?
我跟你一起去
Let's do it together.
什么
Yeah?
我每天都会来看你的
I'll check on you every day.
好
Okay.
走吧
Come on.
我在桌子抽屉里找到的
Found this in my desk.
她人怎么样
What was she like?
烦人得很啊
She was a pain in the ass.
整个警署就数她喝咖啡时毛病最多
Her coffee order was the most complicated in the district.
说要什么咖啡的时间比喝的时间都长
Took her longer to describe it than to drink it.
但她绝对是个好警察
But she was damn good police.
每晚都能问心无愧坦然入睡
Slept like a baby every night.
介意我留下吗
Mind if I keep it?
当然介意
Yeah, I do.
警探
Detective?
跟我一起去博伊特的办公室
Join me in Voight's office.
怎么了
What's up?
罗洛·拉米雷斯的事干得漂亮
Nice job on that Rolo Ramirez thing.
但是你留下了一大后患
Unfortunately, you left a big loose end.
穆尼奥斯  这就是那个纵火犯对吧
Munoz. He's your torcher, right?
是他
That's him.
我们会抓住他的  我各处都有眼线
We'll get him. I got eyes everywhere.
如果我们给所有帮派的人施加压力  就会
If we turn up the heat on every street corner, there'll be--
-拜尔登已经动手了  -拜尔登
- Belden's already on it. - Belden?
这不是我们的案子吗
This is our case.
他说服了副总警监
He convinced the deputy chief
说古斯塔夫·穆尼奥斯也是
that Gustav Munoz here is the same assassin
两周前杀害朗代尔那边牧师的凶手
that took out those priests over in Lawndale two weeks ago.
所以呢
So?
所以这个案子就归他了
So it's his case,
现在那帮哥伦比亚人由他负责
and now the Colombian's his problem.
那我们是不是得乖乖配合他啊
Oh, and we're supposed to cooperate in every way we can.
我倒希望如此
I wish that was it.
你们还记得八爪吧
You remember Pulpo, right?
他绑架过我儿子  还害死了威尔海特
He kidnapped my son. And he killed Willhite.
拜尔登想把那帮哥伦比亚人引出来
Well, Belden wants to draw out the Colombians.
他要把八爪从联邦监狱放出来用做诱饵
He's pulling Pulpo off MCC and using him as bait.
他们要放他出来
They're letting him out?
而且直接越过了我
Went over my head.
也已经被批准了
It's already been approved.